[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
I’m Jenn Rosa.
A feisty woman,
who lives rent-free in your imagination.
Get ready to play with me here at...
“Tatak Jenn Rosa”
Hi! This is Jenn Rosa. There you go.
I’m a Taurus baby girl.
One trait I can say about being a Taurus is that I am humble,
which is why a lot of VMX viewers fall in love and get drawn to me.
I started doing VMX in 2023.
Before that, I was a networker,
and I liked getting into different kinds of businesses.
So I never thought I would enter another industry.
But there came a time when I felt like
I wanted to do something different with my life.
That’s why I decided to get into VMX.
Back then, I was still chubby,
so I didn’t really know how to take care of myself or lose weight.
So when I got into VMX,
I was inspired to take better care of myself,
learn new things,
and explore different things like acting.
And now, you can see the results of being a VMX artist.
Okay, they said I should share my hidden talent.
But guys, here’s the sad part.
You’ve already seen it
because my real talent is being good in bed.
I’m really good in bed— that’s my actual talent, guys.
So I don’t have any other hidden talent to share with you
because you’ve already seen it.
One of the biggest lessons I can share from my experience
is to learn to believe in yourself.
Because no one else can do that for you—
you have to do it yourself.
And, of course, learn to entrust things to the One above.
You also really need to listen to the people around you
who know what they’re doing in the industry.
So, my biggest lesson in life is to believe in yourself.
Do everything with love and always give your best.
You can always see that in the things I do, right?
I always give my best in everything I do.
Like Meg, would you also be able to have sex
with a stranger when you're feeling aroused?
Just like Meg, I could also have sex with a stranger,
but not a Filipino—
I prefer a foreigner,
and organic encounter.
Do you like it when someone watches you play with yourself?
Of course, it feels good when someone watches you
while you’re doing things to yourself.
I also get pleasure from having someone watch me.
And it’s also pleasurable for me when they watches me.
So, it’s a win-win situation.
What's your wildest sexual fantasy?
My wildest sexual fantasy is...
It’s just me but I used to not like the idea of two guys.
But lately, I realized that it actually sounds like an exciting fantasy.
Two hot and handsome guys...
doing all kinds of things to me.
You know what I mean, right?
Shocks, I can already feel it.
No, that’s it. That’s my sexual fantasy.
If Meg loves painting, what are you into?
Meg likes to paint.
I really like reading.
I play sports.
I also really like looking for new things I can learn.
For example, if I don’t know how to swim, I’ll learn how to swim.
If I don’t know how to paddle, I’ll learn how to paddle.
If there’s something I don’t know how to do, I’ll make sure to learn it.
So, I love learning new things.
Those are the things I enjoy doing.
When I was young, my dream was to become a ______.
When I was young, my dream was to become a nurse.
But that dream didn’t come true.
Good thing, because I’m afraid of blood.
I realized that my real dream was to become an actress.
But that dream died.
But now, I’m alive.
When I'm not filming, my hobby is ______. When I’m not shooting,
my hobbies are playing sports,
shopping, of course.
And learning new things.
That’s still one of my regular hobbies.
And I love traveling.
Because I like meeting different people
from different places.
I like learning about their languages and history,
as well as their places.
One thing people probably don't know about me is ______.
One thing people don’t know about me is
that I’m actually smart, joke.
I’m smart, and I’m a curious person.
I like taking an interest in things I don’t know about.
So my curiosity makes me want to find out more.
That’s probably why I look into things and study them.
Because I’m curious.
My friends say I’m too kind
and soft-hearted.
But get ready.
Because when it comes to bed,
I like things hot and rough.
So I’ll make sure that every single part of your body...
is marked by Jenn Rosa!
Just like Brenda, have you ever imagined yourself doing the things she did?
Of course, like Brenda,
I’m just a normal person.
What if your boss is hot and sexy, right?
And he’s handsome, too.
I started imagining him,
and he became one of my fantasies.
But he has to be hot. He can’t be...
just someone or anyone.
He has to be hot and handsome.
What's the wildest place you'd want to have sex in?
What Armani, Nico Locco, and I did in TL…
having sex on a rooftop,
I haven’t done that yet.
But I did it in TL.
And my wildest sexual fantasy is
I want to try it in a public area.
Because I’ve already done it on a fun night out.
I want to try it on a yacht.
With other people
in another yacht.
Have you ever had someone you love get mad at you because you were so focused on work?
Of course not.
Because,
I chose him over work.
So he couldn’t really be angry
because I loved him more than my work.
But now I’m single, so it’s all about work.
Do you prefer being the one on video or being the one taking the video?
Personally, I prefer it when
when I’m doing something,
I’m the one being filmed.
Because, of course, you can see his fantasy
and he’s like, “Wow, damn, she’s so sexy.”
“I’ll film her.”
So I prefer being the one who’s filmed
rather than being the one filming
because filming isn’t my fantasy.
What turns you on? For me, a guy's moan is what turns me on.
I like it when he moans in a satisfying way.
When I hear it,
I think, “Ah, that feels good.”
It’s like I get wet when that happens.
I like hearing the man’s reactions.
So he needs to moan
so I can get even more turned on.
Shit.
Shit!
- You like it? - Yeah.
I'm close!
This will the ultimate plan...
This works every time.
Are you ready to take the lead?
Yes!
Aww yes!
Now, we are going to play “Seduce or Pass”
to find out what kind of guys I’m attracted to
and which ones leave an impression on me.
Rich but emotionally unavailable? I don’t like rich but emotionally unavailable guys
because I’m an emotional person.
So I need emotional support because I’m a baby girl.
Gym buff? Yes, of course.
Because men who take care of themselves are a turn-on.
I like that kind of body—big muscles.
So, seduce.
Super-duper clingy? Of course, I’d seduce him.
Because I like someone who’s affectionate.
I’m a baby girl, after all.
I’m a Taurus baby girl.
Hot body but flirty with everyone? Pass.
I’m jealous, so I don’t like someone who flirts with everyone.
I should be the only one he flirts with.
Are you dominant or submissive?
Honestly, guys, I’m submissive in bed.
I like being handled roughly.
Then just do what you want with me.
I just don’t want to be the one in control.
I just want to lie there.
Pleasure me.
Like that.
Whose sex scene did you enjoy more in this movie? Vern or Aerol?
Whose sexy scene did I enjoy more?
Of course, Aerol. Because he’s a man.
Meanwhile, Vern’s a woman.
And her sexiness in that scene was more demure.
But with Aerol, he gave me a proper spanking.
So, I’m with Aerol.
If you were to photocopy a body part, what would it be?
If I could copy one part of my body, like in Boss Ma’am,
I think I’d choose my back.
Because I think my back is sexy, along with my body shape
and my booty.
How do you actually become sexy?
For me, being sexy is about how you carry yourself.
Sometimes, having a beautiful body isn’t enough to make you look sexy
if you don’t know how to carry yourself and you aren’t confident.
So for me, being sexy means being confident
and knowing how to carry yourself.
And I think the sexiest part of my body is my eyes.
Because I get them with my eyes—my eyes are beautiful.
When the director yells 'cut, ' does the heat you're feeling cut off too?
Aww, sad! I need to stop the heat in my body.
I can control it. I know that when I’m working, it’s just work.
So I also have to turn off that physical excitement.
But it’s a shame. It would be nice.
Mysterious older man? Seduce.
Because I like mature guys. I’m kind of, kind of into them.
So, let’s seduce him.
Handsome but shorter in height?
Pass on someone who’s small, even if he’s handsome.
I’d be bigger than you, and then, you know, right?
So, we’ll pass on that.
No. I like someone bigger.
Not super handsome, but amazing in bed?
Pass!
I feel like I won’t cum...
Seduce or pass. An ex who has changed?
Of course, pass. Even if you’ve changed, you’re still my ex.
So, you’ve already made mistakes in the past.
Pass!
Who do you imagine when pleasuring yourself?
When I need to pleasure myself, I watch VMX,
and of course, I think about myself.
While touching myself.
I don’t really imagine anyone else.
So I just watch porn on VMX.
Have you ever experienced wild outdoor sex?
Not yet, but I experienced it in Las Ilusyunadas.
My back just hurts when...
when you do it by the tree.
But of course, I want to try it.
If given the chance, is there anything you'd want to change in the past?
Of course, I wouldn’t want to change anything about my past.
Because if I changed even one thing, maybe I wouldn’t have experienced all
the wonderful experiences I have now.
Or maybe I wouldn’t be here in VMX, doing sexy shoots.
So I wouldn’t change anything.
Everything was worth it.
What does it feel like when your co-actor is caressing and licking you?
Oh, shocks! Should I admit it?
Of course, I feel so aroused, but it's work.
And there are so many cameramen.
There are so many of them. So I just tell myself, “It’s work.”
Of course, it feels good.
It’s difficult to hold back.
But there’s a cameraman.
What would you do if you woke up and found your friend caressing you?
If my friend starts to...
Of course, I’ll pretend to be asleep for a while.
Because it’s only halfway.
But when he starts licking me,
then I’ll just moan.
So I won’t wake up yet when it’s only halfway.
But when he starts licking me,
I’ll wake up, of course.
Yes, do it, baby!
Never says 'I love you, ' but shows it through their actions?
I want you to say it to me.
Make me feel wanted.
Spoil me.
I won't know unless you tell me.
Pass.
Always says 'I love you, ' but you never feel it?
Pass. I don’t like that.
I like it when you say "I love you" and make me feel it.
Baby girl.
Jealous-type but loyal?
Seduce.
Because it's normal to get jealous.
Because he likes me.
So I must be beautiful.
So it's just normal.
Celebrity crush, but always busy?
Pass.
You should always have time for me.
Of course you’re my crush, give me some time.
An ex-seminarian was the wildest sex encounter I've ever had.
How important is self-pleasure?
For me, self-pleasure is very important.
Because it's kind of like going to the gym.
You need to release the tension in your body.
You know, at the gym, you release the sweat from your body.
So you should do this.
So I do it, like...
Like three to four times a week.
It's just like going to the gym.
What was the profession of your wildest sex partner, and what did you guys do?
The person I had my wildest sex with was a chef.
He's a chef, but he's not Filipino.
So he tossed me around.
It hurt, but...
that's where the thrill was.
It felt good. So he tossed me around.
He's a chef.
He's good at cooking.
His body is nice.
If you were to make a self-pleasure tutorial video, what would you teach?
If I made a self-pleasure video tutorial...
I feel like you've seen it already.
But okay, let’s do it.
Pleasure for myself.
Like this... and then...
There, like that.
You should watch Kirot.
Angelica's self-pleasure video is over there.
If you were to get another tattoo,
where are you putting it and what design would it be?
If I were to get another tattoo,
I really want “amor fati.”
It's like... "love of fate."
I want to have it placed here.
But they told me not to.
Because it's like...
I look dirty, there are so many of them now.
But I really want “amor fati.”
It means “love of fate”.
You accept everything that has happened in your life.
Whatever it may be, good or bad.
Everything has a reason.
What's a 'first time' experience you want to do?
Two boys and I'm the only girl.
But they have to be handsome.
Gym buffs.
And they should be foreigners.
And they have to be huge.
I want to try it.
Why not? Right?
It feels amazing.
Now, let's play Act-moji.
I will act the Emoji that will be flash on your screens
Okay, let's go.
Act-moji 1.
That's my answer for Act-moji 1.
Seduce us with your moan.
I’m ready guys.
Let’s go.
That’s it.
Cliffhanger!
What are the chances you'd also have sex with a coworker?
Zero, it’s difficult to mix things with a co-worker.
We should be professional
So, I haven't had sex with any of my coworkers yet.
So, I'll just do it with someone else instead of my coworker.
Let’s see, maybe next time.
Do you have any sex-perience with a girl?
And relationship?
Yes, I've had one. But I only did it for about three or four months.
I was just curious before because I used to watch a lot of porn.
I watched girl-to-girl porn.
I thought, "Shocks! Maybe I'm attracted to women. Or maybe I want them."
So I tried being with a girl, but she was very feminine, like a lipstick girlfriend,
so she was more feminine than me.
Because at that time, I'm somewhat boyish.
So yeah, it was okay.
I actually enjoyed it.
- Show us your sexiest pose. - Okay, let's do this.
Let me just show you—here.
Because this is my thing.
What keeps you grounded, even though you’re already one of the well-known VMX Queens?
Oh wow! That's intense... one of the 'VMX Queens?'
Of course, what keeps me grounded is my family.
And everything I've gone through in life and in showbiz,
especially having to start over,
particularly when you start as a supporting actress.
And of course, the fact that I'm here now,
and that I get to entertain and make my fans happy.
So those are the things that keep me grounded.
That's why I remain humble, because I didn't ask for all of this.
The Lord blessed me with this.
This was given by God.
I was faithful so I should always be humble.
And of course, thank you to my bosses at Viva.
They trusted me.
Act-moji.
I think this is it.
Like that
Yes!
How far would you go for your partner?
What Faith did…
Maybe in her situation, she could do that.
But for me, I don't think I could put my body through that for my partner
because they should be the one providing that for me, not me.
So I don't think I could do it.
But what I can do out of love for my partner
is that I can have their face tattooed here.
But he’s not around anymore. That's it.
It was covered up and turned into a koi fish.
So that’s how it turned out as a tattoo on my body.
That’s why I got a tattoo.
Right? You know the story behind it.
Be honest... who was the best co-star to do intimate scenes with in Backrider?
Be honest, who's better?
I think it’s Aerol, because we had wilder sex
That’s why, it’s Aerol, Chad was just okay.
So definitely Aerol.
Now you know, Aerol.
Maybe give me something, just kidding.
Who’s better in bed? Gentle good boy or rough bad boy?
Who's better in bed?
I haven't experienced it yet— a good boy who's gentle
or a bad boy who's rough?
So, what about a bad boy who's rough?
I like bad boys.
If you were a masseuse,
which local celebrity would you want to give a massage to?
Special service from a local artist.
None, because I'm not really a fan of local celebrities.
Since I’m into girls...
maybe I’ll massage Marian Rivera, just kidding.
As for men? Let's see...
No one comes to mind.
Maybe Channing Tatum, he’s a foreigner.
As I told you before, I prefer foreigner than Filipino.
So of course, if it's Channing Tatum,
he wouldn't even need to say anything.
There would already be extra service right away.
Even if it's just for fun.
How was your sexual experience in the gaming chair and pool table?
The sex scene Aerol and I had on the gaming chair and pool table.
It was a little painful on the gaming chair.
Our scene went really well because it didn't look painful at all.
But it was still difficult to do.
But maybe if what happened between us were real,
because those kinds of things aren't real.
If it were real, I think it will be pleasurable.
But painful.
So that's it, it was okay.
Okay, Act-moji...
I feel like this is it.
I have a feeling that's it.
As for , I didn't find it difficult to shoot the movie.
and the sex scenes
Ah, there's actually one that I had difficulty with.
The one on the bamboo.
Because it was painful, then my partner was pulling my hair,
and it was so rough.
It was painful to the knee.
But I love all my scenes in Helena.
Especially the last part.
That’s why, please watch Helena.
Do you use baby oil for sex?
In real life, I don't use oil when having sex,
because it's sticky.
I sweat easily.
But for sure, next time I'll try it, when there are two boys.
I will use it as a lubricant.
Slippery, for sure.
If there are two boys, surely I will some oil.
Receiving oral sex or giving it?
I prefer receiving it.
Because that’s my favorite position
That’s why I prefer receiving oral.
Giving head comes second.
It's your first time playing as a healer.
What other "firsts" do you want to experience in life?
First time? First time... yeah!
It's my first time playing as a healer.
The first thing I ever wanted to do in my life...
Two boys, both of them. Let's stick with that, guys.
Let's stick with two foreign guys— it feels so good.
And handsome.
Hot.
Nice!
Eat my pussy.
Like that.
Go on.
Put it in.
Put my leg over your arm.
There.
Yeah!
- Like this? - Yes!
Faster.
Are you still thinking about the heat of my moans, my touch, and my body?
Remember, I still have many more seductive secrets to reveal.
So keep following me.
Once again, I'm Jenn Rosa, and this is Tatak Jenn Rosa.